GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
By the way...
how did you find me?
I saw a bus.
And I noticed...
that you fell asleep.
Next time, think about where to switch off.
You keep falling asleep!
No, what if I wasn't there?
Fine. I won't sleep again.
Listen, let's get to those competitions
haven't met?
I didn't notice that you
you live in the next house.
We met.
Is it true?
You somehow confused me with the courier.
Don't remember?
When is this?
In the spring. When we moved.
Here's how.
It's a pity that we didn't know each other.
Tell?
Have you ever visited our store?
- What?
- I often sit at the cash register instead of my mother.
"BASIC INSTINCT"
Never bought a DVD from us?
Makes me sleepy.
You...
Are you sleeping?
The eyes close.
Come in.
We miss a lot in life.
Sun Jae seemed like a star in the sky to me -
so far away.
It turns out that in my youth,
full of unpleasant memories
Sun Jae was nearby.
All you had to do was reach out your hand.
He breathed the same air
looked at the same sky
walked the same road.
Knew my name.
Salt! Lim Sol!
But then I didn't know...
that he was the one who saved me.
Only having encountered again
with the past, I realized
so many fateful moments
didn't notice.
Why are you crying?
Maybe they shouldn't be missed.
And all this time they are from afar
glowed brightly,
giving me a sign.
It shouldn't be missed either.
This is the reason...
which is why we met again.
SERIES 5
Song Jae! Ryu Sung Jae!
Song Jae!
Hello!
Come out quickly!
What's this time?
Look at the sky, rainbow!
Beautiful?
You wouldn't have seen it if it weren't for me!
Make a wish!
It would be visible.
What? Can't see it?
No.
Wait.
Song Jae!
So how? Do you see now?
I see.
What's happened? Where does the water come from? God.
Asshole! What did you do this morning?
Stop it! All!
Come here!
Salt! What are you doing? Salt!
Mom, mom! Wait!
No, no, no, mom!
Mom, you understood everything wrong!
No, mom, wait!
Wait! Mother! Wait, wait!
Don't be a mother! How old are you? What is this?
- Mom, I'm now...
- God!
- Mother!
- Salt!
I'll explain everything now. Mother!
- Really, sorry! Sorry!
- Sorry?
- Well, mom!
- Stand!
Song Jae!
Here you go.
What kind of gifts are these in the morning?
It came from your roof.
This... This is not mine. This is grandma's.
She loves pink.
Who... Who... Who asked? God.
Crap. What a day...
I just wanted to go with you.
There is one thing.
And which one?
That's it.
Thank you, Sung Jae.
For what?
For saving me.
And I'm also sorry.
I should have said this earlier
It's already late.
She said it yesterday.
Yesterday is yesterday.
Aren't you avoiding me?
He said you're not friends with girls.
Are we friends?
So, all the rumors are about relationships
turned out to be true.
You had a lot of girls.
It will be like in the legend. You saved me.
Forty will not remain in debt.
There's a swallow there.
Really?
It blew by.
So...
...swallow.
Have you decided to plant pumpkins right away?
This is a capsule. Time capsule.
There's a gift inside.
All the treasures in fairy tales
hidden in pumpkins.
If it's a gift, why bury it?
I'll pick it up.
I'm telling you, it's a time capsule.
You dig too.
What's inside? Treasures, right?
No, this is even more valuable than treasures!
You will be surprised when you open it.
When to open?
In 2023?
What kind of gift is this?
These are shares. Blue chips.
Let them sit there and go up in price.
Seriously?
No.
January 1, 2023.
At midnight. Near the Han River.
Let's open it together.
Why first?
ECLIPSE'S Ryu Sung Jae Passes Away
To change your destiny.
So please, be patient for another day.
Only then does the gift make sense.
You'll definitely love what's inside.
So wait.
Don't open it until then!
January 1, 2023. At midnight.
Near the Han River. Understood?
January 1, 2023. At midnight. Near the Han River.
Wait. By then we will be lost.
Who knows what will happen?
Even if we stop communicating,
be sure to come.
Think of it as an alumni reunion.
And I am your old friend.
Who said we were friends?
I'm busy.
If you meet Lim Seol,
ask how she is.
Why? Call Tae Sung.
He started dating Lim Seol
just like that.
- What?
- I got tired of Choi Ga Hyun and decided
switch to Salt.
That's it.
And you...
Forget it. Let's go.
She doesn't even understand.
Salt! Where are your eyes?
Here?
Wait for me!
- What about the duty officers? Constant checks.
- Don’t talk!
Exactly! I forgot my tie.
I'll have to run in the morning.
Wait.
What are you going to do?
I'm an athlete.
I never wore a uniform.
Nothing.
Where's the tie? You're not at the market.
What a dunce. I would have hit him anyway.
Go! Stupid.
Ryu Sung Jae.
You're not an athlete anymore, brat.
Dress appropriately. Understood?
- Yes.
- Good morning.
What people!
You usually climb over the fence,
gentlemen, idiots?
We...
...we give up.
Will you take us with you?
Of course!
Please!
It barely drags along.
You'll have to run one more lap!
Why did you drag me into this?
For you to move.
Crap.
Buddy.
At least pretend.
And we don’t even know each other.
And with my girlfriend too?
Are you running after her?
Exactly. You live nearby.
What do you want?
What do I want?
I'm wondering
Do swimmers run well?
A turtle, for example, can barely crawl on the ground.
You too?
Stop smoking!
Damn it.
What's wrong with your face?
- Examination.
- Move away, asshole.
What other check?
Yes, yes. Lim Sol you like.
- What?
- Just look at yourself.
You go to school every day,
you don't smoke cigarettes,
Don't fool girls.
- Strange things!
- That's it, that's it.
Get dressed, come on.
There is no need to scare people.
All sweaty.
- Don't like it?
- Get dressed, I say.
- The rest have no chance.
- Yes.
The champion is back in the game.
See, our Park Tae Hwan
in a red cap.
Attention. In places. Get ready.
Switch off. Let's. What is it?
So. Park Tae Hwan takes the lead.
- Crap!
-He's going for the gold medal!
Switch off! Let's!
I'm home.
Hello. How are you?
What are you doing?
I?
Well... The TV is broken.
What's on the floor?
These are rats.
Forward, forward, forward, come on!
What a handsome man! Lucky parents
such a handsome son was born.
Look! Park Tae Hwan tomorrow
will take the gold, for sure!
Certainly!
Swimming gold?
Oh well, our swimmers are only
They are reassuring and know how.
- Or maybe he’ll take it!
- Not only gold,
We’ll also take silver!
What a moron.
The shares will then skyrocket.
Exactly!
UPDATED COLLECTION OF PROBLEMS
REMINDER TO APPLICANTS
Sun Jae, are you free tomorrow?
What's happened?
Shall we go to the cinema?
What? To the cinema?
Yes, I chose the film.
I...
Tickets have been purchased.
Let's go.
Let's.
Is the guy busy?
Why suddenly a movie?
I wanted to thank you.
Park Tae Hwan!
Song Jae! Lace!
What?
Don't bow.
Funny?
Let's go. Faster. Let's go.
What's wrong with you?
Park Tae Hwan?
What?
Look how I can move my eyes.
Cool?
I can go the other way, look!
Wow, like that, oh, like that, like that!
Summer is in full swing, it's hot outside -
suitable weather for dates.
Dear listeners, call me quickly
your loved ones,
and enjoy together
warm days...
Very soon at the Olympic Games
2008 in Beijing
The 300 meter swim starts.
Korean swimmer Park Tae Hwan...
"THE GOOD, THE BAD, THE FUCKING"
You could say whatever you want
go to the cinema.
I would at least get some sleep then.
I thought you wouldn't want to.
Of course I want to, what do you want?
I love movies.
- Yes? Great.
- Dear viewers,
please make sure you are seated
in their places.
You are now in Hall No. 1.
In case of alarm, please go
to the nearest door
and proceed to the nearest
emergency exit.
- What?
- What's happened?
- Should I go out?
- Do you have to get up?
What?
- Sol, get up.
- Let's go!
- Let's go, let's go.
- Come out!
Dear viewers, the alarm is sounding.
We apologize for the inconvenience.
- Tae Hwan!
- Forward, forward!
- Look, look!
- Wow!
- Let's!
- Like this!
Park Tae Hwan! Come on, come on! Yes! Forward!
- It's floating!
- God!
- God, Park Tae Hwan!
- God, wow!
Park Tae Hwan, go ahead!
There's still a little bit left
swim, swim, come on!
- Yes!
- Park Tae Hwan! Park Tae Hwan!
Park Tae Hwan took gold! Our hero!
Incredible, Park Tae Hwan...
You brought me to the cinema because of the games?
Did you and dad come to an agreement, or what?
Well, I won't look
but if we take the medal,
the whole country will know!
I understand, but I still wanted...
What? Did you think it would make me cry?
Even...
if I had known in advance
anyway...
started swimming.
Honestly...
I found joy in sports.
Without him I would never have known happiness.
And I don't regret it.
Not about what I started
nor about the fact that he quit.
Therefore...
everything is fine.
Remember.
INSTITUTE OF RESEARCH
ACTING "METHOD"
As soon as I see him...
Is class over?
Yes. Did you come to the course too?
No, I want to give you something. Here you go.
And I already thought that my shirt
They sent me to India to do the laundry.
- A very long time!
- I have exams soon.
I have nothing to do
just run after you!
Hyun Joo, how long ago have you become so important?
You talk like you're talking to an elder...
Wow! Did you buy a new one? Well done!
I see I'm on the right path.
How did you know that I would be happy?
Well, did you finally get your tooth fixed?
Yes.
By the way, your uncle is simply a master.
That's good. I'll go.
There are actually people walking here!
How are you?
Everything... Everything... Everything... Everything...
Everything is fine with me!
- What's wrong with her?
- And why is my heart beating like that?
I haven't seen anything in the cinema for a long time.
It's a shame.
Do you like movies?
Yes. I used to have two or three films
I watched it a day.
I dreamed of becoming a director.
Why did you dream?
To begin with, I would like to do it on my own two feet
get to class,
where will the exam be?
I also thought about the exam.
Exam?
I want to go to the Faculty of Physical Education.
Is it true? My brother finished it.
Do you want to become a teacher?
Don't get ahead of yourself.
I can't imagine myself in something
except swimming.
What are you talking about?
Robe, fireman's uniform,
police officer, even hanbok!
Everything suits you, really!
You say you saw it.
No no. So, if you want to do it,
you need to score a minimum score.
Get ready! Should I help you?
- Will you help?
- Yes! Yes, sure.
I'll remember.
Hello...
What?
What to do?
COMPUTER REPAIR AT VON'S
What are you doing?
- Go.
- What are you doing?
Go!
Song Jae. Song Jae. Is mom gone there?
- Yes, she left.
- Gone?
God bless. Finally.
Can you imagine, I was so scared...
My leg went numb.
God...
Oh my god, Sung Jae! Aren't you in pain?
No.
I really didn't want to hit you
advance, Sung Jae!
My God! God! My God!
God! God! Song Jae!
Please forgive me, I didn't mean to.
I'll tear up now, wait.
Well done. Well done!
Go Korea!
Go Park Tae Hwan!
Forward!
I'm home.
Forward?
Go ahead, son!
Forward!
-Are you going to your place?
- Yes.
Dad...
Just turn on the telly.
Do your eyes hurt?
Did I watch something?
I didn't look!
You have an antenna in your pants.
This... This is me looking for water veins.
We should have them under our house.
Don't worry, watch TV.
And it only spoils your eyes!
I'm telling you, I didn't look
and you don't believe me!
The TV is broken, I don't watch anything.
Earned it!
Wow. Wow! Already fixed it?
Dad.
Everything is really good.
Okay, don't worry.
Don't do that again.
- Rest.
- OK.
ANNIVERSARY OF THE DEATH OF THE POPE
Salt. Call for you.
The police are calling.
From the police?
So, they found it near the reservoir and brought it back.
But there is no phone.
There was a drunk man with me
didn't you find it?
No camera footage?
What kind of cameras are there in that area?
He buried the body and disappeared without a trace.
- What?
Listen, I'm because of this incident
I'm already going crazy.
- Go.
- Can I call quickly?
Yes. Call. Call.
Thank you.
Yes? Hello?
Hello, can you hear me?
Here's the thing...
Hello? Hello?
What the hell is this? Found nothing
decided to pick up an ancient phone?
If my mother finds out, she will arrange a home for me.
Move away, please.
This is weird.
What's happened?
- How did he bury it? My God.
- Look on that side.
- Some kind of nightmare.
- There is no road there,
How did he even get there?
There is nowhere to go on that side.
How did he think of burying the corpse?
- Dead body?
- Horror. It's definitely not local.
Wait! What if it was one of the fishermen?
People often fish here!
In terms of?
My God.
What kind of memory is this?
It seems like the day of the accident.
We haven't gone grocery shopping for a long time.
You followed me
just not to study?
Actually, I wanted to help you with the packages
like an exemplary daughter!
Me too, exemplary. Did you find your phone number?
No, just a wallet.
Well done, well done, I understand you.
I’ll buy a new one after the exams, just know that!
Okay, okay.
So, let's see.
My God.
Apples are good in summer. We must take it.
Give me some apples, please.
Those that are larger. Yes.
-Are you not dating anyone?
- What?
It would be good if you found a rich man
and a handsome guy.
Salt. Today is the anniversary of my father's death.
If you have anyone in mind, go ahead.
You're still young. In the prime of life!
In its prime?
So, powerlifting.
Gold. We'll take the gold, for sure.
Jang Mi Ran will lift 175kg!
He grabbed it and lifted it confidently.
Brilliantly! Nice push!
This is Jang Mi Ran from Korea!
The athlete takes a breath.
Next - 183 kg!
- Another 8 kg have been added.
- Can he handle it?
So what do we see?
Great, I grabbed the barbell.
And he picked it up!
Eat! Eat! Picked it up! Picked it up!
- What a push, look!
- Wow!
Now Jang Mi Ran has to
lift 186 kg!
Our athlete fights for victory,
but also struggles with himself.
And we, along with the audience, are rooting for him.
and with all our hearts we wish you good luck.
So...
Grabbed the barbell!
- Like this.
- Push.
Jang Mi Ran lifted the weights!
Gold medal!
New Olympic record!
This is Korean Jang Mi Ran,
installed in a day
several world records!
World record!
Come on! World record! Wow!
Listen...
Wow.
I remember you.
What?
It was you who got my sister drunk, yes, yes!
Hey, I saw you bring Sol home.
All red and cheerful!
When did this happen?
Come on. And what will happen to me from this?
- Then?
- Do you remember? Yes?
Set aside.
Attention.
Leave it alone!
Attention!
She got drunk herself, honestly.
Are the talkers in ranks?
Fell.
Got up.
I did push-ups!
I'm just after surgery...
Put aside the push-ups, stand up!
Are you dating?
No. More.
More?
Wow, everything went into me.
Popular.
Who is she dating then?
- With someone else.
- With someone else? With whom?
The one that put out the fire here?
I'll tell you, he's nothing like that.
- In what place?
- Cute,
knows how to dress, popular.
It also puts out fires well!
Today you are nasty!
Wha... What?
Attention!
Lim Geum!
Do you suddenly imagine yourself as a commander?
In the army I did nothing but
I ate for free!
You're talking like you're talking to your older brother.
asshole?
Lim Geum, get it!
It hurts, mom! You are young
did you play volleyball?
Such pitches!
Shut your mouth!
Father will come down to the funeral dinner,
and will return with frayed nerves!
Come here. You are shameless.
Let's go and get down to business.
Mom, let me go!
- Quiet. Forward!
- Mother!
Mom, let me go!
- Go, don’t be a mother!
- Well, mom!
Cute, knows how to dress,
popular.
Cute.
No. Don't look.
Sun Jae, don't look!
No.
CONGRATULATIONS! YOU ARE HAPPY
100,000 VISITOR!
30 LUCKY ACORNES BY KIM TAE SONG
Did you like it?
- No!
- Is this Kim Tae Sun? Seriously?
Look, it's Kim Tae Sun.
RYU SUN JAE
What is he doing here?
- Cute.
- How handsome. Look!
LIM SALT
- Just a little more!
- No!
The subscriber's phone is switched off.
Leave a message...
I don't understand anything.
It can't be so beautiful!
Where are you?
In your heart?
Don't piss me off, come on faster!
For what? Yesterday we rehearsed.
I haven't memorized the chords yet.
What are you going to do?
I give it 15 minutes.
Listen, I have to go.
Mom said she would come to pick me up.
Then we'll try without a bass player.
Enough.
Tone Sop.
Wrong note.
Sorry, I took it a little higher, right?
No! You sang too low!
Vocalist...
Maybe we should invite Sun Jae?
Dad.
You know, I'm a little scared.
I'm afraid I won't be able to protect him.
Please help me.
Can you ride?
Yes. Are you not?
No.
On weekends my dad taught me.
But I was so afraid
that I couldn't learn.
I dreamed that dad would see
how I ride.
It's too late now.
You're on time.
He sees everything from heaven.
Song Jae!
Get off for a minute.
What?
OK.
That's why it's hard for you.
The seat is too high
You can get hit hard.
That's it, sit down.
Thank you.
- Comfortable?
- Yes!
I'll insure you, go ahead.
Will you teach me?
Let's see if I'm any good
the teacher will come out.
And you won't scold me,
what if it doesn't work out?
Won't you scream?
Do you know what is important for a swimmer?
- What?
- Calmness.
CALM
You're driving! Rules! Rules! Rules!
Steer and pedal. Left.
Now the right one. Turn the right pedal!
Right!
No...
Yes. Look.
You twist the left one and immediately twist the right one,
don't forget to steer.
- It's easy!
- It would be easy
I would have learned long ago!
Calm.
There is no peace left!
Fine. Again.
I'm on my way!
Right pedal.
No skills left!
I won't study.
How's that? And endurance too?
Who will hire you as a physical education teacher?
No skills left?
Everything works out for me!
Fine.
One more time?
Like this.
Yes! Yes! Well done! Well done!
It works out well. Yes, yes, yes.
Well done! You're going great, yeah!
Well done! Well done!
Fell. What can I do?
Still fell.
That's it, yes.
- So?
- Yes, yes.
Well done.
Don't let go. I can't do it myself.
I won't let go.
You didn't let go, did you?
Well done!
- Did you let go?
- Look ahead.
Yes, yes.
Speed ​​up.
Look!
This moment...
no way...
I shouldn't miss it.
- God!
- Carefully!
I learned.
Well done.
I'll ride some more.
Exactly? Your legs will hurt.
I know. I want them to be sick.
Careful, careful. Drive in a straight line.
Examination?
- Sure?
- Let's.
Well no! Where are you going?
JONGHYANG READING ROOM
Remember.
Let's.
Students received results
entrance exam 2009.
There was some controversy about the difficulty level
questions in a math test...
There is no hope for mathematics.
We need to switch to another subject.
LITERATURE
I'm crazy. Why am I thinking about him?
Forget. Forget it, she said!
Hyun Joo. What's wrong with you?
Maybe we can go for a walk?
No! Disappear, disappear!
What's happened?
I need a distraction.
Hello.
Who are you going to impress?
You can't get out of your sweatpants.
Come visit us!
Don't answer, don't even look them in the eye.
Go ahead
until you like something.
Even if you want to buy, hold back.
Otherwise they'll rip you off. Let's go.
- Yes, yes.
- This is it!
Didn't you listen to me?
This bomber jacket?
Great choice.
Uncle will give you a good discount.
Come here.
Go, go. Let's.
- OK. I'll take a walk for now.
- Go.
When I saw you,
immediately introduced it.
Your boyfriend is performing today.
That's why I came.
Yes?
I came because Hyun Joo called.
Sol is preparing for exams,
so don't even call her!
Okay, aunt.
Go crazy.
Song Jae!
Are you going to the concert?
Yes.
Crap.
You'd think I was dating him.
Change your clothes.
Why?
Are you confident?
Make sure you don't lose.
Aren't you ashamed to carry such nonsense?
Please your order.
Thank you.
So.
What are you doing?
Sit down.
I'm sitting with such handsome guys now,
who else is Lim Geum?
Hello.
I'm Seol's friend, Lee Hyun Joo.
Hyun Chu?
She's around handsome guys
loses his head.
Hasn't changed at all.
Clear.
Wait.
Here.
You don't like sweets.
Thank you.
Where is Baek In Hyuk? Are you not together?
Got lost in the store.
By the way.
How do you like my gift?
Did you like it?
Present?
I make the fans happy.
It turns out that Sung Jae is one of them.
I declined your gift.
- Didn’t notice?
- Come on?
You got dirty.
Poor single people, it’s hard for them.
Do you have a girlfriend?
No.
It's clear.
Do you like someone?
You don't want to answer.
OK.
By the way.
Where are In Hyuk and Dong Seop?
And what am I talking about?
- Guys.
- Crap!
Catastrophe!
You're a disaster.
What style is this? Comedian uncle?
That's not the point!
Dong Seop won't come!
- What?
- Mama's boy.
He says his mom found out everything.
and didn’t let me go anywhere.
I'll go crazy. What should we do?
Maybe I should sing instead?
For us to embarrass ourselves?
We'll just cancel the show.
Crap.
OK.
No, wait, wait!
Hello? Where are you?
Where's Sun Jae?
Thank you very much
for an excellent performance.
Let's welcome the next group,
they prepared something no less interesting...
It's starting soon, where did he go?
It's Eclipse!
Who is this? Ryu Sung Jae?
Great performance!
You are awesome.
She probably left.
We've already met.
At the school.
Ryu Sung Jae sings well!
And Baek In Hyuk is cool!
Let's go out and talk.
- I...
- It's fast.
CEO Kim?
- Sung Jae...
- Died tragically.
- No. No. No.
- Lim Sol!
- How are you?
- Everything is fine?
What, were you waiting for me?
Have you met anyone?
I thought you had already left.
Did that strange man approach you?
How did you know?
Did he offer you a debut?
You want?
What nonsense.
He gave me a business card, but I didn't call back.
What is it?
Just. There are a lot of strange people now.
And there are plenty of scammers among them.
I was worried.
I'm not a child.
No need to worry so much.
Here you go.
This is a gift.
Is that why you decided to perform?
- Yes.
- Is this why you sang in front of the whole audience?
I didn't do anything for you!
- I thought you would be without a phone...
- So what?
I said it myself, don’t worry so much!
And what?
Can't I worry about you?
Yes. It is forbidden.
Don't think about others and don't do anything.
If you don't give free rein to your feelings,
they will continue to torment you,
so much so that you can’t sleep,
and in the end you just give up!
So stop it!
What are you talking about?
It's just a gift.
I want...
so that you think about yourself.
I want you to
At such moments I thought only about myself
and about your happiness.
About your life!
Did you think about yourself?
Is it true?
Yes.
It's clear.
I was wrong.
Throw it away. Do what you want.
JN-IM ENTERTAINMENT
I was thinking about myself. Is it true?
- I thought you would be without a phone...
- So what?
I said it myself, don’t worry so much!
And what? Can't I worry about you?
Hello.
This is mine!
This is my idol!
You start again.
What?
- Still?
- Wow.
Straight from the picture.
Can you still move?
Funny. Very fun.
How to remove it?
Song Jae...
Should I think about myself?
Will you break up?
If I want this, will you break up?
Salt.
Leave Kim Tae-sung.
You...
I like you.
GRAB SUN JAE AND RUN
Does Sun Jae like me?
Does such a bright guy like me?
He understood everything.
- Let's talk.
- She doesn't want to.
- Go away.
- Come with me.
Tae Sung will figure it out.
What if they touch her?
What's the matter, seriously?
- Hello.
- No salt, I'll go.
- Don't go.
- I wanted to wait a little longer...
but I can't do it anymore.
You tell me...
Sun Jae, I'm sorry, I won't go out.
Don't wait for me.
Translated and voiced by the studio
"Mobile TV"
commissioned by the online cinema Ivy
in 2024.